British Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Britain (Box 1)
  - Paintings (Box 1)
    - 19th – 20th century (6 photographs) (Box 2)
      - A (88 photographs) (Box 3)
        - U – V (11 photographs) (Box 85)
          - Whistler, Rex, 1905- (5 photographs) (Box 87)
          - Wilkie, David, Sir, 1785-1841 (21 photographs) (Box 87)
          - Wilson, Richard, 1714-1782 (61 photographs) (Box 87)
          - Wint, Peter, de, 1784-1849 (5 photographs) (Box 88)
          - Wootton, John, ca. 1682-1765 (12 photographs) (Box 88)
          - Wright, John Michael, 1625-1700 (6 photographs) (Box 88)
          - Wright, Joseph, of Derby, 1734-1797 (50 photographs) (Box 88)
          - X – Y – Z (18 photographs) (Box 89)
          - Yeats, Jack Butler, the younger, 1871-1957 (6 photographs) (Box 89)
          - Zoffany, Johann (John), 1733-1810 (6 photographs) (Box 89)